<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes"?>
<property contact="0395642288"/><Type>Unit</Type><Price>1230</Price><address>165Riversdale Road,
				Hawthorn,VIC,3122, Australia </address><NumberOfBedrooms>4</NumberOfBedrooms><numberOfBathrooms>2</numberOfBathrooms><garage>2</garage><description>This recently renovated home is very private and spacious inspection is a must! This double story brick veneer home is located in a convenient location, comprising four bedrooms 3 with built in robes, large master bedroom with Ensuite, s/system heat/cool, walk in robe, access to large private balcony and ample in roof storage at the top of the stairs.</description><property contact="0398051111"/><Type>Unit</Type><Price>410</Price><address>6/23Grattan Street,
				Hawthorn,VIC,3122, Australia </address><NumberOfBedrooms>5</NumberOfBedrooms><numberOfBathrooms>1</numberOfBathrooms><garage>1</garage><description>Located on the ground floor, is this stunning, light-filled and beautifully renovated two bedroom apartment in the perfect location. Features spacious lounge with floating timber floors, feature wall and private balcony. Gorgeous kitchen with stainless steel appliances including dishwasher and gas cooking plus meals area. Large double master bedroom and generous second bedroom with access to rear private courtyard and both with mirrored built in robes. Sparkling recently renovated bathroom with seperate shower and bath as well as laundry taps. Private rear courtyard leading around the side of the complex which is all yours!</description><property contact="0434700434"/><Type>Unit</Type><Price>430</Price><address>4/30Ryeburne Avenue,
				Hawthorn,VIC,3123, Australia </address><NumberOfBedrooms>2</NumberOfBedrooms><numberOfBathrooms>1</numberOfBathrooms><garage>1</garage><description>This gorgeous top floor Art Deco offering in a boutique block of 6 is placed in a superb and exclusive location. Barely moments away from restaurants, cafes, and shopping within the lively Camberwell Junction, and close to exclusive schools such as Carey and Camberwell Grammar. Recently updated, the sublime open living area with beautiful hard wood flooring flows into the intimate dining area, in addition to excellent kitchen - with Westinghouse appliances and Fisher and Paykel dishwasher - that opens to the southern balcony. Two generous bedrooms offer built in robes, serviced by a relaxing bathroom. This prized residence provides sealed access entry, lockable single garage space, and a tranquil shared courtyard</description><property contact="0394899422"/><Type>Apartment</Type><Price>420</Price><address>4/85Pleasant Road,
				Hawthorn East,VIC,3123, Australia </address><NumberOfBedrooms>2</NumberOfBedrooms><numberOfBathrooms>2</numberOfBathrooms><garage>1</garage><description>This pleasant sun drenched 2 bedroom, 2 bathroom apartment is ideally situated close to Bourke Road/Camberwell junction, trains, trams.Tree lined, street frontage, first floor apartment boasts to 2 spacious bedrooms with built in robes (floor to ceiling mirror door), spacious open plan living leading out through French doors to a large private balcony fit to entertain guests.Other highlights include fully equipped kitchen complete with quality appliances, dishwasher and ample cupboard space. Two (2) bright bathrooms, one with shower over bath, European laundry, heating and cooling throughout, fully screened, secure undercover parking and remote intercom access.</description><property contact="0398170123"/><Type>Apartment</Type><Price>400</Price><address>5/13Monteath Avenue,
				Hawthorn East,VIC,3123, Australia </address><NumberOfBedrooms>2</NumberOfBedrooms><numberOfBathrooms>1</numberOfBathrooms><garage>1</garage><description>This lovely 2-Bedroom Apartment is a must to see. You step into a hallway from a private balcony and the floor plan opens up to provide a large, flowing and sunny living and dining area with a functional contemporary kitchen. The stainless steel gas cook top and under bench oven are complimented by plenty of cupboards and work bench space. Both bedrooms lead from a rear hallway with the west one capturing views across to the city. Both have excellent built-in wardrobes. A lovely modern, crisp white bathroom sits between the bedrooms. A secure apartment in an exceptional location. Here you are literally just a stone's throw from the heart of Camberwell Junction's renowned shopping, restaurant, cafe, theatre precinct and all forms of transport with Camberwell train station just a short stroll away. Located on the top (second) floor, entry is via a private balcony providing added security to the intercom access downstairs. There is a communal laundry downstairs and undercover parking for one car. Open for Inspection times are subject to cancellation without notice.</description><property contact="0398170123"/><Type>Apartment</Type><Price>400</Price><address>5/13Monteath Avenue,
				Hawthorn East,VIC,3123, Australia </address><NumberOfBedrooms>2</NumberOfBedrooms><numberOfBathrooms>1</numberOfBathrooms><garage>1</garage><description>This lovely 2-Bedroom Apartment is a must to see. You step into a hallway from a private balcony and the floor plan opens up to provide a large, flowing and sunny living and dining area with a functional contemporary kitchen. The stainless steel gas cook top and under bench oven are complimented by plenty of cupboards and work bench space. Both bedrooms lead from a rear hallway with the west one capturing views across to the city. Both have excellent built-in wardrobes. A lovely modern, crisp white bathroom sits between the bedrooms. A secure apartment in an exceptional location. Here you are literally just a stone's throw from the heart of Camberwell Junction's renowned shopping, restaurant, cafe, theatre precinct and all forms of transport with Camberwell train station just a short stroll away. Located on the top (second) floor, entry is via a private balcony providing added security to the intercom access downstairs. There is a communal laundry downstairs and undercover parking for one car. Open for Inspection times are subject to cancellation without notice.</description><property contact="0398170123"/><Type>Apartment</Type><Price>420</Price><address>8/23 Osborne Avenue,
				GLEN IRIS,VIC,3146, Australia </address><NumberOfBedrooms>2</NumberOfBedrooms><numberOfBathrooms>1</numberOfBathrooms><garage>1</garage><description>This updated bright and spacious apartment has just been repainted. Including spacious entry hall, two double bedrooms with built in robes, modern kitchen with meals area, sunny living room with views, northern balcony, updated bathroom and laundry. Also features two separate carports, split system aircon,security entry,and close proximity to Harold Holt pool, tram and train station.</description><property contact="0398051111"/><Type>Apartment</Type><Price>410</Price><address>13/88Victoria Road,
				Hawthorn East,VIC,3123, Australia </address><NumberOfBedrooms>2</NumberOfBedrooms><numberOfBathrooms>1</numberOfBathrooms><garage>1</garage><description>This freshly painted 2 bedroom apartment is set on the first floor of a very well maintained block. Both bedrooms have BIR's, main bathroom has spa bath, separate shower and toilet and laundry facilities. Kitchen with electric cooking, ample cupboard space and a leafy outlook. Floating floors throughout, with new carpet in the bedrooms. Situated at the rear of the block, sharing a security entrance with only 1 other flat. Air conditioner in the living room and undercover parking. Minutes from prestigious Burke Road shopping, public transport and Geebung Polo Club.PLEASE NOTE: Open for inspection times are subject to change or cancellation without notice.</description><property contact="0398240900"/><Type>Apartment</Type><Price>465</Price><address>212/339Burnley Street,
				Richmond,VIC,3121, Australia </address><NumberOfBedrooms>2</NumberOfBedrooms><numberOfBathrooms>1</numberOfBathrooms><garage>1</garage><description>Stunning 2 bedroom, 1 bathroom in the near new apartments on Burnley Street. Walking distance to Swan Street and Burnley rail station. This large light filled apartment comprise spacious lounge with private balcony, kitchen with stone bench tops, pantry, gas hotplates, stainless steel appliances including electric oven and dishwasher. Generous sized bathroom and shower. European laundry, heating and cooling throughout. Car space/stacker and storage cage.PLEASE NOTE: Open for inspection times are subject to change, please check inspection times prior to viewing.</description><property contact="0398240900"/><Type>Unit</Type><Price>499</Price><address>C308/609Victoria Street,
				ABBOTSFORD,VIC,3067, Australia </address><NumberOfBedrooms>2</NumberOfBedrooms><numberOfBathrooms>2</numberOfBathrooms><garage>2</garage><description>Brand new luxury apartment ideally located within a short stroll to Victoria Gardens shopping precinct and public transport. Comprising entrance/hall, spacious lounge opening to private balcony ideal for entertaining, open plan kitchen with ample cupboard space, two good sized bedrooms (master with walk in robe and ensuite bathroom), stylish main bathroom with shower over bath and euro laundry. Other features include split system (heating/cooling), dishwasher, gas cooking, security entry, secure off street parking and storage.</description><property contact="0398105000"/><Type>Unit</Type><Price>500</Price><address>2/174-178Riversdale Road,
				HAWTHORN,VIC,3122, Australia </address><NumberOfBedrooms>2</NumberOfBedrooms><numberOfBathrooms>2</numberOfBathrooms><garage>1</garage><description>This stunning ground floor residence offers a fresh start without comprising on outdoor space. Open plan living with split system leading to outdoor terrace and private front yard, adjoining kitchen with stainless steel appliances (dishwasher), two bedrooms (mirrored BIRs), separate bathroom and European laundry. For your security Luma offers video intercom entrance remote security parking with lift access for two cars, bike rack and your own storage cage. With cafes and trams at your doorstep, be quick to move in and enjoy this light filled apartment at Luma.</description><property contact="0398105000"/><Type>Unit</Type><Price>460</Price><address>10/69Wattle Road,
				HAWTHORN,VIC,3122, Australia </address><NumberOfBedrooms>2</NumberOfBedrooms><numberOfBathrooms>2</numberOfBathrooms><garage>1</garage><description>This generous 2 bedroom villa unit located close to Glenferrie Road boasts a bright living area with polished floor boards opening to a low maintenance courtyard, fully renovated kitchen with gas cooking and dishwasher, built in robes to both bedrooms, bathroom and separate laundry. Added features include gas heating and a carport. All this within easy access to shops and public transport.</description><property contact="0398105000"/><Type>Unit</Type><Price>430</Price><address>1/174-178Riversdale Road,
				HAWTHORN,VIC,3122, Australia </address><NumberOfBedrooms>2</NumberOfBedrooms><numberOfBathrooms>2</numberOfBathrooms><garage>1</garage><description>This generous 2 bedroom villa unit located close to Glenferrie Road boasts a bright living area with polished floor boards opening to a low maintenance courtyard, fully renovated kitchen with gas cooking and dishwasher, built in robes to both bedrooms, bathroom and separate laundry. Added features include gas heating and a carport. All this within easy access to shops and public transport.</description><property contact="0398105000"/><Type>Unit</Type><Price>400</Price><address>11/9AFordholm Road,
				HAWTHORN,VIC,3122, Australia </address><NumberOfBedrooms>2</NumberOfBedrooms><numberOfBathrooms>2</numberOfBathrooms><garage>1</garage><description>Enjoy the high life in this spacious first-floor apartment peacefully nestled to the rear of sought after Fordholm Court. Northern light streams through the generous space of this fabulous apartment which has been updated for quality living. Located close to Glenferrie Road shops, trams, private schools and Fairview Park this stunning apartment offers two sizable bedrooms (BIRs), flowing open-plan living and meals, kitchen with gas cooking and stainless-steel appliances, immaculate bathroom, as new window furnishings throughout, euro laundry, gas heater, polished hardwood floors and single carport.</description><property contact="0398105000"/><Type>Unit</Type><Price>375</Price><address>3/69Morang Road,
				HAWTHORN,VIC,3122, Australia </address><NumberOfBedrooms>2</NumberOfBedrooms><numberOfBathrooms>2</numberOfBathrooms><garage>1</garage><description>Brilliantly positioned opposite Morang Park, close to Yarra River, Hawthorn Station, trams and shopping, this lovely refurbished sun drenched 2 bedroom strata apartment (1 of only 6) features generous living and dining to balcony with views, well equipped kitchen, 2 spacious bedrooms with BIR's, central bathroom, secure entrance and car park.</description><property contact="0398105000"/><Type>Unit</Type><Price>925</Price><address>7/4Shakespeare Grove,
				HAWTHORN,VIC,3122, Australia </address><NumberOfBedrooms>3</NumberOfBedrooms><numberOfBathrooms>2</numberOfBathrooms><garage>1</garage><description>This freshly painted one bedroom apartment comprises a spacious light filled open plan lounge and dining area with electric wall heater, new light fittings, new window furnishing and floating timber floorboards throughout. The adjoining kitchen has recently been updated and offers electric upright oven and stovetop and decent cupboard/bench space. There is a large master bedroom with BIR, central bathroom/laundry and single off street parking. Located only a short walk to Hawthorn train station, City bound trams, shops, cafes, schools and parklands this wonderful apartment is positioned perfectly. Opportunities like this dont come up often so get in quick before this delightful apartment is gone!</description><property contact="0398105000"/><Type>Unit</Type><Price>630</Price><address>1/831Toorak Road,
				HAWTHORN EAST,VIC,3122, Australia </address><NumberOfBedrooms>3</NumberOfBedrooms><numberOfBathrooms>2</numberOfBathrooms><garage>2</garage><description>This light filled modern two storey townhouse is situated within walking distance to public transport and the nearby Tooronga Village Shopping Centre. Comprising large open plan living with lounge room and dining area opening out onto a paved private courtyard with aesthetic garden surrounds. The spacious and stylish kitchen offers stainless steel appliances, electric oven, gas cooktop and the convenience of a dishwasher. Walk upstairs to find master bedroom with WIR and ensuite and two additional bedrooms both with BIR, with the third slightly smaller bedroom ideal for a study or home office. The main bathroom is centrally located and offers both shower and spa bath facilities. There is also a separate laundry, two powder rooms and single remote garage with internal access. Other features of this stunning townhouse are additional off street parking, security gated entrance with intercom, private front garden, ducted heating and cooling and polished timber floorboards in the downstairs dining area. This sophisticated modern townhouse has everything you need and is definitely not one to miss, strictly no pets.</description><property contact="0398105000"/><Type>Apartment</Type><Price>390</Price><address>1/830Toorak Road,
				HAWTHORN EAST,VIC,3122, Australia </address><NumberOfBedrooms>3</NumberOfBedrooms><numberOfBathrooms>2</numberOfBathrooms><garage>2</garage><description>This light filled modern two storey townhouse is situated within walking distance to public transport and the nearby Tooronga Village Shopping Centre. Comprising large open plan living with lounge room and dining area opening out onto a paved private courtyard with aesthetic garden surrounds. The spacious and stylish kitchen offers stainless steel appliances, electric oven, gas cooktop and the convenience of a dishwasher. Walk upstairs to find master bedroom with WIR and ensuite and two additional bedrooms both with BIR, with the third slightly smaller bedroom ideal for a study or home office. The main bathroom is centrally located and offers both shower and spa bath facilities. There is also a separate laundry, two powder rooms and single remote garage with internal access.
</description>
